{
    "subject": "resource/Royal_Netherlands_Air_Force",
    "predicate": "property/aircraftTransport",
    "object": "resource/Lockheed_C-130_Hercules",
    "human_readable": "The Royal Netherlands Air Force transports Lockheed C-130 Hercules.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872795343399048,
            "question": "Is the Lockheed C-130 Hercules used by the Royal Netherlands Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9697396755218506,
            "question": "How many Lockheed C-130 Hercules aircraft does the Royal Netherlands Air Force operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8448721766471863,
            "question": "Which organization operates the Lockheed C-130 Hercules?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7785807251930237,
            "question": "Are there any other air forces that operate the Lockheed C-130 Hercules?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.759358286857605,
            "question": "Where are Lockheed C-130 Hercules aircraft manufactured?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7164624929428101,
            "question": "What are some common uses for the Lockheed C-130 Hercules?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6991415619850159,
            "question": "What is the history of the Lockheed C-130 Hercules?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6542742848396301,
            "question": "What is the name of the aircraft transported by the Royal Netherlands Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6307545304298401,
            "question": "What type of aircraft does the Royal Netherlands Air Force transport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6177399158477783,
            "question": "What is the primary function of a Lockheed C-130 Hercules?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Royal Netherlands Air Force transports Lockheed C-130 Hercules.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3571_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of aircraft does the Royal Netherlands Air Force transport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3571_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the aircraft transported by the Royal Netherlands Air Force?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3571_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of the Lockheed C-130 Hercules?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3571_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3571_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe triple states that The Royal Netherlands Air Force transports Lockheed C-130 Hercules. This statement is supported by multiple documents, including:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3571/re-ranker-msmarco/112.txt, which mentions \"All are on the strength of 336 Squadron based at Eindhoven. The Dutch Hercules has seen operational use in Rwanda, the former Yugoslavia and Afghanistan amongst other theatres.\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3571/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt, which mentions \"The squadron, based at Eindhoven air base and equipped with four Lockheed C-130H/C-130H-30 Hercules transport aircraft...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to the Royal Netherlands Air Force operating Lockheed C-130 Hercules aircraft, thus supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}